MATTHEW MOMNEY

Technical Project Manager

Windsor, ON +1 519 563-7087 mattmomney@hotmail.com

Passionate and dedicated technical project manager with 3+ years' experience overseeing the development process and 7+ years in development. Collaborating on multiple projects at once has provided me with effective organizational and interpersonal communication skills. Proficient in both Waterfall and Agile methodologies using the latest project tracking tools and technologies. Expert in user experience, web standards and best practices.

EXPERIENCE

Alteris Group Canada, Remote

Application Developer / Technical Project Manager

June 2017 – August 2023

- Led the onboarding and training process for new developers working on eLearning projects, driving successful project delivery.
- Conducted in-depth market discovery research for potential future projects.
- Provided valuable UI/UX analysis and support, ensuring adherence to industry standards and guidelines for projects and the company's design system.
- Collaborated effectively with cross-functional teams including Writers,
 Designers, Quality Assurance, and Project Managers to resolve technical issues and deliver client satisfaction.
- Developed fully responsive websites and applications with asynchronous data transfer, utilizing the latest tools to streamline development and ensure engaging user experiences.
- Created and maintained alterisgroup.com website.

Alteris Group Canada, Windsor Ontario

Web Developer Contractor

December 2015 - June 2017

- Successfully developed and managed eLearning projects, delivering highquality results efficiently.
- Demonstrated exceptional attention to detail by implementing designs precisely for engaging and interactive fully responsive websites and applications.

Red Lobster, Windsor, ON

Kitchen Staff / Kitchen Expeditor September 2008 - September 2017

- Facilitated efficient order flow and clear communication between waitstaff and kitchen, ensuring seamless operations.
- Ensured strict adherence to health and safety standards by overseeing the performance of kitchen staff.

SKILLS

HTML5/XML CSS3/SASS/SCSS JavaScript/jQuery

Vue.JS ReactJS Node.JS Ruby PHP .NET/C# SQL

WordPress JIRA Adobe CC Sketch

GIT

Microsoft Office Google Suite

ABILITIES

Excellent oral and written communication.
Well-organized.
Attention to detail.

EDUCATION

St. Clair College

Advanced Diploma, Internet Apps & Web Development

April 2016

Windsor, ON

- GPA: 4.0
- Completed 3-year program